字幕制作墨迹未干╰
QQ:574855297
2010年 在发生过一系列无法解释的事情后
包括牧场主８岁大的孩子离奇失踪
这个“皮行者牧场”开始备受媒体关注
现代国防企业（MDE）派遣了一组专家前往记录和研究这个现象
MDE录像被发现在一位叫做雅各布朗戴尔斯
的记者手里，他通过秘密的资源渠道获得的。
2013年1月18日，朗戴尔斯意外失踪
警告：接下的录像可能会对一些观众造成不适。
2010年11月11日
11月11日，这天是科迪特殊的日子
This is Cody's special day,November 11th
跳啊
Jump.
爸爸！爸爸！
Dad! Dad!
额，我就在这
Well, there he is.
等等，今天是你生日吗？
Wait, is it your birthday today?
你答应会做到的！你答应会做到的！
You got to make it!You got to make it!
我告诉你了啊，我告诉你我会帮你准备的！
I told you.I told you I would get it.
生日快乐！
Happy Birthday.
在你下个生日我给你请一整个棒球队来这儿
Next birthday we'll have a whole team of guys here.
到时候我们就一起在这儿打棒球
We'll all be playing baseball together.
准备好！
Get set.
跑起来!
Go！
啊...
Argh!
我有点拉伤，我应该...
I pulled a muscle.Got to do...
什么...那到底是什么鬼东西？
What...What the hell was that?
科迪？科迪？
- Cody?- Cody?
科迪？科迪！
Cody? Cody!
不！
No!
2011年8月1日，MDE开始展开调查
不，我认为霍伊特对此没有任何办法。
Nah, I don't think Hoyt had anything to do with it.
嗯，孩子突然失踪让人痛心，但这也是事实。
Uh, sad but true,kids are kidnapped.
额，就在那发生后，你知道的
Well, right after it happened,'cause, you know,
这些事情致使他被无奈的送进了法院
they had to, like, drag him into court and all that stuff...
所以在大家面前他很无助，还有对这些事情
so he's kind of forced to be around everybody and all that stuff...
你知道的，不同的是他对这件事情有另外的看法。
there was a difference. And there was some mean in him then, you know.
直到那次我遇见一个醉鬼，才提醒我记起他来着
I didn't consider him, up until that time, a drunkard or anything.
后来我们有次去递送干草，他还有没从阴影走出来
I didn't talk to him at length about it, but, you know,
所以你知道的，关于这个我没怎么过问
we were delivering hay, and he was just broke up.
你知道，要让我亲身经历我才会相信的
You know,show it to me and then I'll believe it.
你问我，我认为他...他很愧疚
You ask me, I think he's... he's guilty.
也许每个人对霍伊特都感到恐惧
Maybe everybody's projecting their fear on Hoyt.
也许那都是注定的
Maybe that's what's going on.
那就是他独自生活的缘由
That's why he's left alone.
但是在他找到孩子前他都会住在那儿的
But he's staying there until he finds his boy.
我是说很可悲，真的很可悲。
I mean, it's sad.It's sad as can be.
我也有孩子和外孙
I've got kids and grandkids.
要是我的一个8岁的外孙不见了的话，我应该....
And if an 8-year-old grandkid of mine disappeared, I'd be...
嗯，我不知道我该干嘛
Yeah, I don't know what I'd do.
科迪和我年幼的女儿在一个班
Cody was in my little girl's class.
你要知道，我几乎每天晚上去她的房间里
I've been having to go in and sleep with her almost every night,
陪着她直到她睡着。
you know, 'til she falls asleep.
所以呢，嗯，很不容易
So, yeah, it's been hard.
当然了，伙计，我认识科迪
Of course, I know Cody, man.
他可是个好孩子，还很有趣
He's a good kid.Funny.
那个小不点本该健健康康成长的
Little wiry. He was gonna grow into them feet one day.
是的,伙计
Yeah, man.
是的,我认识科迪
Yeah. I knew Cody.
我是说我多少了解他一点
I mean,I've followed it quite a bit.
我真的不买你的账, 我对超自然现象不感兴趣
I don't really buy either one. I'm not into the paranormal stuff.
我没看过那卷磁带, 我也没看过像那样的狼
I've never seen that tape. And I've never seen a wolf like that.
嗯...
Um...
但这些可能还会发生
But it could happen.
如果这些事情还会在哪儿发生的话，那就在这儿
Could happen around here if it's going to happen somewhere.
那....你知道的，我不相信这一整件事
That's... I don't believe any of it, you know.
我必须要看到什么才会相信的
I got to see something to believe it.
我没见过像那样的东西
I've never seen anything like that.
伙计，你呆在这的话你会看到什么的
You stick around, man,you'll see something.
2011年8月2号
我叫萨姆格林
My name is Sam green.
我是个来自芝加哥大学的
I'm a PH.D.In socio-cultural anthropology
社会文化人类学博士.我已经为MDE做
from the university of Chicago. I've been working for MDE
实地科学家大约有6个月了.
for about six months as a field scientist.
抱歉
Sorry.
我的伙计
My man!
嘿，萨姆！
Hey, Sam!
哥们，最近怎么样？
How are you, buddy?
- 伙计很高兴见到你。 - 我也是。
- Good to see you, man.- You, too.
我叫做卡梅隆墨菲，嗯...
My name's Cameron Murphy. Um...
我是来自洛城的前线记者
I'm an investigative journalist from Los Angeles.
我和萨姆一起长大，大约一个月前他通知我
Sam and I grew up together.He called me about a month ago.
告诉我说他正前往一个奇怪的牧场进行一项实地调查。
Told me he was heading up an investigation to some strange cattle ranch.
问我会不会来这儿以第三方的视角关注这件事情
Asked me if I would come out and observe it from a third party perspective.
嘿，这是我们的摄像师布莱顿
Hey, this is our videographer Britain.
嘿，伙计。卡梅隆，很高兴见到你。
Hey, man. Cameron. Nice to meet you.
我叫做布莱顿斯洛恩。我是个自由职业的摄像师
My name's Britain Sloan. I'm a freelance cameraman.
一般来说不喜欢站在摄像头前
Normally don't like to be in front of the camera.
所以我会简短点
So I'll make this short.
在和其他组员在一起前，我干过这个
I've done this kind of work before with other groups.
我们从来没遇到过奇怪的或者违常理的事情
And we've never come across anything strange or out of the ordinary.
所以我希望这次出行会有点不一样
So I hope this trip is a little different.
嗨，伙计，你能帮他拿下包吗？
Hey, man, would you grab his bag for him?
当然
Yeah.
- 有劳了，伙计  - 这地儿的小风景怎么样
- Thanks, man. - How about a little tour of the grounds?
- 还可以。 - 知道了
- Yeah. - All right.
霍伊特
Hoyt!
我想你见见我的朋友卡梅隆墨菲
I want you to meet my friend Cameron Murphy.
-嘿，卡梅隆。 - 很荣幸见到你，霍伊特
- Hey, Cameron. - Hoyt, pleasure.
霍伊特米勒。那是我的名字，霍伊特米勒
Hoyt Miller. That's my name.Hoyt Miller.
嗯，还有，我买下了这，嗯...
And, uh, I bought this, uh...
这个牧场，哦，有四年...四年多了
This ranch, oh, four years... little over four years ago...
你知道的，那时还有着把它改造的想法
with the idea of turning it into something, you know,
现在感觉很不一样或者...要我说，嗯...
special or... say, uh...
我不得不说吗？
Do I have to do this?
我...我现在必须在镜头前说话吗？
Can I... do I have to talk to the camera right now?
我真的不是很喜欢这样
I don't really feel like it.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
好的，大家伙在45分钟内准备好
All right, you guys be up in about 45 minutes.
车子已经备好了
We'll have the ATV ready.
- 听起来很不错。 - 狗儿，过来
- Sounds good. - Come on, girl.
这是我们的主要兽医工作人员丽萨
This is our main vet tech Lisa.
丽萨，卡梅隆。
Lisa, Cameron.
哦，卡梅隆，我听过很多关于你的事情
Oh, Cameron, I heard a lot about you.
我叫丽萨莫罗，是个实地兽医工作者
My name is Lisa Moreau. I'm the field veterinary tech.
我在这儿工作有些年头了
I've worked locally for years.
几个月前，我刚开始和MDE成员一起工作
I just started working with MDE a couple months ago.
这是和他们在一起我的首件大事
This is my first big case with them.
他们会把我带到这儿是因为我深入研究过这的牛群肢解现象
They brought me on because I'm so familiar with the cattle mutilations in the area.
那很烦人
It's disturbing.
在我的工作上，我见过太多生病和死亡的动物
I've seen a lot of sick and dead animals in my line of work.
但...这牛群肢解现象...
But... The cattle mutilation phenomenon is...
我还不能做出合理的解释
I don't have an explanation for it.
马的状态还异常吗？
Is the horse still acting unusual?
额，不是。这些马的情绪稳定下来了
Uh, no. The horse's moods stabilized.
额，他们的行为曾经非常古怪
Um. Their behavior's been completely erratic.
所以，现在一切都好。咱们等等再谈谈
So, it's fine now. But you talk to me in 10 minutes.
- 行，到时候。 - 好的
- All right, I will. - OK.
嗯，你见到马特了吗？
Uh, you seen Matt?
是的，我想雷正让他在房子前弄些什么东西
Yeah, I think Ray has him setting up something behind the house.
- 很荣幸见到你，丽萨。 - 见到你很高兴
- Lisa, pleasure. - Nice to meet you.
伙计，你呆在阿富汗有些日子了吧
That's a long time to be in Afghanistan, man.
事实上，我加入那十来个士兵的小队
Actually, I was embedded with a group of about 10 soldiers
差不多有三个月的时间
for a period of nearly three months.
- 情况还好吗？ - 你是说这些该死的运动传感器吗？
- How's it going? - You mean, motion sensor hell?
嗨，我叫马特约翰逊。
Hi, I'm Matt Johnson.
我在MDE的媒体实验室工作，我在那儿认识萨姆的
And I work in the media lab at MDE, which is how I met Sam,
他把我带到这儿来进行这项研究
who brought me on board the project.
我们两对超自然现象都很热衷
We both share a passion for the paranormal.
还有，额，我真希望这项研究
And, uh, well, I really hope that this project
对这地儿的现象有点帮助
helps legitimize the field a little bit.
在队里我担当司机、厨师和该死的队医
Also I'm here as the team's driver, cook, and resident bitch.
你准备好了吗？
You ready?
准备好了。
Copy.
那是什么？
What was that?
我的手，在那上面
My hand, over.
在墙前面走几步，你个蠢蛋
Walk in front of it, you stupid ass.
那是雷。我们去看看他。
That's Ray. Let's go meet him.
雷，来看看卡梅隆墨菲
Ray, I want you to meet Cameron Murphy.
嘿，伙计
Hey, man.
伙计，你是负责传感器这块的吗？
You here to help with the sensors, man?
雷里德，退伍军人
Ray Reed. Ex-military.
负责安全和情报还有骂人
Here for the security and wires and shit.
如果幸运女神眷顾我们有什么发现的话，我们就要在这儿呆上一段时间了
If lady luck shines upon us, this place is gonna be a God damn fortress.
那就是我要说的，结束了没？
That's all I got. We done?
嗯。
Hmm.
摄像头弄的怎么样了？
How are the cameras coming?
快好了。你们结束这个后
They're almost set up. When you guys are done,
为什么不去摄像头上露个脸，我会把录像给你看的
why don't you pop on by and I'll show you.
下午好，霍伊特
Afternoon, Hoyt.
准备好启程了吗？
Ready to roll?
走吧
Let's go.
好的。大家都上来了没？
All right. Everybody in?
我们这是要去哪？
Where we headed?
霍伊特在牧场发现了一头死鹿
Hoyt found a dead deer on the property.
萨姆想去看看死鹿的情况
Sam wants to check it out.
这儿的总面积有多少亩？
What's the acreage?
大约1000亩左右
About 1,000 give or take.
嗯，虽然我下面要说的还没有明确的定义
Well, it's not clearly defined.
但是爱达荷州南部，尤因塔盆地，四角，
But parts of Southern Idaho, the Uintah basin, four corners,
直到内华达州和加利福尼亚都被认为是
all the way to Nevada and California is considered
美国超自然现象圣地
the paranormal Mecca of the United States.
今天当地政府甚至从来没有管过这儿
Local tribes won't even set foot on this land to this day.
对于他刚刚说的圣地有什么直接证据吗？
There's evidence for this?
我们都知道，嗯，回到18世纪迹象表明
We got, uh, evidence going back to the 1800s
这儿有第一次UFO观光记录
with the first documented UFO sightings.
47年的罗斯威尔事件
Roswell crash in '47.
67年的首次牛群肢解事件
First reported cattle mutilation in '67.
达格韦基本上是新的51区
Dugway is basically the new area 51.
51区：一处极为重要的秘密军事基地
从没听说过这个
Never heard of it.
来这儿途中你刚好经过那儿
You passed it right on the way up here.
美国军方研究的爆心投影点
Ground zero for U.S. military research.
我是说我们所谈论的事情都是有人亲眼所见、亲耳所闻的
I mean, we're talking everything from remote viewing to psychological warfare.
就在那小土丘上面
Just over the ridge here.
萨姆，很对不起扫了你的兴。它是自然死亡
Sam, I'm sorry to burst your bubble. But she died of natural causes.
你注意到它舌头变色了吗？
Do you see the discoloration in the tongue?
这是典型的出血性疾病
It's a classic case of hemorrhagic disease.
无论怎么都取点样
Take a sample anyway.
好的，是你想要的话
Sure, whatever you want.
嘿，嗯... 我们最好回去
Hey, uh... We'd better get back.
我感觉有大风暴来临
We got a big storm coming.
谢谢，霍伊特
Thanks, Hoyt.
没事
All right.
所有的生活记录直接上传到这台服务器上
All the feeds record directly into the server here.
以防万一，我把这些都备份在C-70上了
Just in case, I got it all backed up on the C-70.
它由发电机供电
It's generator powered.
是独立的材料制作的，已被设定好了24小时实时监控
It's all independently wired, and it's set to record 24/7.
摄像头1是一个大范围的道路镜头
Camera one's a wide shot of the road
所以我们可以监控进出牧场的人
so we can monitor everyone coming in and out of the property.
摄像头2是房子周边
Camera two is wide of the house.
摄像头3是西牧场
Camera three is of the Western pasture.
摄像头4是畜栏
Camera four is of the corral.
摄像头5是饲料仓外部
Camera five is the barn exterior.
摄像头6就是饲料仓里头
And camera six is inside the barn.
这是为了更好配合外部的摄像头
That's it for the exterior cameras.
在晚上又是什么情况呢？
What happens at night?
他们会变成红外摄像头
They all switch to infrared.
我想这就是X射线吧
This is the X-ray I was talking about.
真的不是我该管的
Not really my thing.
哦，让我看看
Oh, let me see it.
嗯，给他吧
Well, just pass it along.
谢谢
Thanks.
如果可以的话，我想和大家伙干上一杯
If I could, I'd like to propose a toast.
嗯，我就想，嗯
Uh, I just want to, um...
感谢大家来到这儿
Thank you all for coming up here.
嗯
Uh...
在我的孩子失踪后，
Since my boy's been gone,
我得到的帮助很少就快没有了
the help's been few and far between.
我... 我真的很感谢你们的帮助
And I just... I really appreciate it.
我想让你们知道这点
And I want you to know that
无论发生什么事情，我希望大家伙会一直在这儿的
whatever this thing is, I believe it's still here.
还有那东西很聪明
And it's really smart.
事实上
As a matter of fact,
我打赌那东西正在注意着我们
I would bet my arm that it's watching us right now.
所以...
So...
哦，不。不要把我仍在这儿。
Oh, no. Don't leave me up here.
干杯吧！
Cheers.
- 干杯      - 干杯
- Cheers. - Cheers.
你想我去那儿？
Where do you want me to go?
就走动一下，我好看到你
Just walk and I'll find you.
明白
Copy.
这是起居室吗？
This is the living room?
嗯。
Yes.
对你的小伙伴说你好
Say hi to big brother.
快点
Say it.
嗨
Hi.
卧室1
Bedroom one.
卧室2
Bedroom two.
用餐间
The dining room.
厨房
Kitchen.
嘿，马特，你可以听我说下楼去吗？
Hey, Matt, can you go downstairs for me, please?
可以。
You got it.
霍伊特的房间
Hoyt's room.
科迪的房间
Cody's room.
来到地下室
Got the basement.
这是老屠宰间
And this is the old butcher room.
哦，我的天
Oh, my God!
抱歉。真的很抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
我没想... 我只是对着摄像头
I didn't mean... just the cameras.
我认为你知道我在这儿
And I thought you knew I was here.
没事。就不要像那样静悄悄的接近人
It's all right. Just don't sneak up on people like that.
我知道。那很愚蠢。抱歉
I know. It was stupid. I'm sorry.
- 好的 - 雷，该死的。干这个
- All right. - This works. God damn it, Ray.
伙计，你刚好呆在盲区
The blind spot's going to be on you, man.
如果你想看任何录像，和我说就行了
If you guys need to review any footage, just let me know.
我就会把它放到这儿
And I'll set it up right here.
我可以侦测出牧场大部分区域的运动迹象
I got motion detectors across most of the property.
有什么动静的话，我会知道的
So if something moves, we're going to know about it.
我也调用了大部分传感器去侦测大型物体
Also I programmed most of the sensors to detect only large objects.
我倒想看看外面的动物们晚上都有些什么活动
I don't want the local wildlife having us chase ghosts all night.
好的
All right.
用餐间
我想去睡觉了
晚安。霍伊特
好的...伙计们明天见
那是...嗯
有些人认为他造了假录像是真的吗？
但总有这些怀疑论者
好，要是他真的这么做了呢
为什么他要那么做
我不知道
萨姆，要是我们有证据的话人们将会认为他疯了...
那就是这些人所期望的
我们是来帮忙的
吃你一个
8月2号
August 2nd.
这是我来这牧场的第一个晚上
It's my first official night here at the ranch.
- 嘿 - 嗨
- Hey. - Hi.
你在这儿自言自语吗？
Are you in here talking to yourself?
嗯，不。 事实上我是在对着摄像头说话
Um, no. Actually it's the camera.
我用摄像头来记录行程
I use it as a video journal.
哦，那笔和纸用来干什么的呢？
Oh. What happened to the days of the mighty pen and paper?
- 那还是很有用的东西。或者...  - 果断点说，我不需要它们
- Is that still a thing, or... - Sadly, they are gone.
嗯。好的，只要你不用这东西
Hmm. Well, as long as you don't use this thing
来大半夜拍照就行
for any midnight photography...
苍天为证
Scout's honor.
哦，好的
Oh, good.
- 我已经录了相了。 - 的确
- I got that on tape. - You did.
- 那上面也录了。-好的
- And tape. - Right.
所以你认识萨姆多久了？
So how long have you known Sam?
几个月
A couple months.
听着，额，我真的更希望关掉摄像机
Listen, uh, I actually would prefer this to be off.
就是这个按钮
It's actually this button.
好的，谢谢提醒
Well, that is good to know.
那该死的是什么？
What the hell was that?
在屋顶上！
They're on the roof!
嘘
Shh.
该死的到底是什么
What the hell is it?
那是...
Is that the...
嘘
shh.
该死
Shit.
哦，我的天。在这儿！在这儿！
Oh, my God. You guys. You guys!
我去拿梯子
I'll get the ladder.
布莱顿，小心点上去
Careful going up, Britain.
等等，丽萨，什么...
Wait, Lisa, what...
马特，不要。是蝙蝠
Matt, don't. Rabies.
霍伊特，你以前从来没遇见过像这样的事情吗？
You ever seen anything like that before, Hoyt?
真的没有。没遇见像这样的
Hell no. Nothing like this.
没有任何创伤。内部结构都是完好的
There's no trauma. The internal organs are fine.
是声波扰乱了它们的声纳系统
It was definitely the tone that messed with their sonar.
额，哈
Uh-huh.
这才是刚开始而已
This is just the beginning.
我想睡下觉
I'm gonna get some sleep.
祝你好运
Good luck with that.
我想去记录这个声波事件
I'm going to document it as the tone.
好的，没问题
Yeah, absolutely.
我需要你再去看看
I need you to check more.
我已经看过了
We've already checked...
你好。请在一段语音后留下您的录音
hello. Please leave a message after the tone.
你好！米勒先生，我是白橡木精神病院的大夫戴维
Hello, Mr. Miller, this is Dr. David at white oak psychiatric.
我想告诉你你妻子这几个月来的进步
I wanted to talk to you about your wife's progress over the last month.
如果你能在你最方便的时候给我的电话的话
If you could give me a call at your earliest convenience,
我会很感激
I'd appreciate it.
哦，我的天。对不起
Oh, my God. Sorry.
好的。没事
Ok. It's ok.
- 你们都还好吗？ - 是的
- You guys all right? - Yeah.
好的，因为我要你们跟着我去牧场
Good. 'Cause I'm going to need you to follow me out to the pasture.
发生什么了？
What's going on?
MDE之前没有提到会派其他人来这个牧场啊
MDE never mentioned anyone else coming up to the property.
那不像是他们的作风
I don't think that's them.
他已经在这儿有三四十分钟了
He's been sitting out there about 35, 45 minutes.
没有什么保护层。那是军用车吗？
There's no plates on it. Is that thing military?
不知道。我没有头绪
I don't know. It's hard to tell.
哦，也许是某人迷路了呗
Well, maybe it's someone who got lost.
他开动了。正在掉头呢
He's on the move. He's turning around.
萨姆，等等，等一下。我有个问题
Sam, wait. Hang on. I have a question.
雷，你怎么看？
What do you think, Ray?
不知道，但是不该那样做的
I don't know. But it's not right.
嗯，那肯定是不对的
No. It sure ain't right.
太没礼貌了，我从没见过有人像那样冒然闯进来
I've never seen anybody out there like that. No way.
注意，我是关于这件事情的头儿
Look, I'm team leader of this thing.
如果你是头儿，那你应该知道的
If you are the team leader, then you're supposed to know...
听着，霍伊特，我不知道来这牧场的每辆车的情况
look, Hoyt, I don't know every vehicle that's going to come on to the ranch.
嘿，冷静。听着，弄清楚先
Hey, calm down. Listen, figure it out.
好的。我对昨晚那件噪音事件进行过了分析
OK, so I ran an analysis on that tone from last night.
证据表明我们的录像里面真有2道声波
Turns out there were actually two sounds on that tape.
高音调的噪音很显然我们都知道，就是把我们吵醒的那种
There was that high-pitched noise that we obviously know, the one that woke us up.
但是在这噪音的下面我发现了次声波
But below that I found traces of infrasound.
次声波？
Infrasound?
是的，它的频率比人耳可听见频率范围还低
Yeah, it's a frequency below the audible range of the human ear.
那什么可以引起像那样的声波
So what could cause something like that?
我想，次声波可能自然产生或者人为制造
I mean, infrasound can occur naturally or it can be manmade.
你懂的，军方通过每秒特定的周期
You know, at certain cycles per second,
事实上已经成功的制造出了次声波
the military has actually successfully tested infrasound
来引起负面影响诸如眩晕，沮丧，恐惧，不安，
to cause things like vertigo, depression, fear, anxiety,
身体病变，咽喉压迫等各种各样的可怕影响
physical lesions, throat pressure, all sorts of awful side effects.
我是说，这些只是我所了解的
And, I mean, those are just the ones that we know about.
好的，那又是怎样自然产生的呢?
Ok. And how about naturally?
所有我们知道的大型自然灾害
All the big natural disasters that we know of...
火山，地震，雪崩
volcanoes, earthquakes, avalanches.
那就是为什么动物们可以在人们采取措施前侦测地震
It's why animals are able to detect earthquakes before people do.
他们可以感觉到振动
They pick up the vibrations.
动物...鲸鱼...它们发出听不见的声波
Animals... whales... they use inaudible sounds
来麻痹并且抓住特定的猎物，你知道的像鱼这样的
to paralyze and catch certain prey, like, you know, fish.
我是说我们听马特所说的声音
I'm just saying that the sound we heard
可能是被活着的动物发出的
that Matt's talking about could've been caused by a live animal.
真不知道我们是在这儿做些什么
We have no idea what we're dealing with here.
鲸鱼他妈的怎么跑到这儿来的
How the fuck would a whale get up here?
我们要在这儿干点什么吗？
So what are we doing out here?
哦，据说如果直接尝试去
Oh, it's really well documented that attempting
和超自然能量交流的话真可以
to communicate with paranormal energies directly
加大遇见它们的可能性
really increases likelihood of contact.
跟我来
Follow me.
跟在你后边
After you.
萨姆要我来牧场的，并做些祈祷
Sam has asked me to come and do a blessing on the property
以便和这片大地上会私语的能量交流
to communicate with the energy that speaks from this earth.
但你要知道
But you need to know.
这片土地被人们遗弃
This land is forsaken by my people.
这只是试着给你们带来
And it's only to try and bring you some protection
一些我能做到的保护
that I've agreed to come.
这儿有勇士们在这山谷里打猎
There are legends of warriors hunting in this valley,
回到他们变得凌乱不堪的部落的传说
returning to their tribe disturbed and changed.
并且整个部落消失的故事
Stories of whole tribes disappearing.
这片土壤充满这黑暗
There is a darkness in this soil.
如果不叫你们离开可能你们感觉无关紧要
I would not feel right if I didn't suggest that you leave now
或者这样说，这个地方除了给你们带来灾难之外一无是处
or to say that this place has nothing for you but suffering.
我也知道你们已经决定留在这儿
I also know that you've chosen to stay.
我会尽我所能给这里多带来一点希望，不管有多少
And I'll do what I can to bring some light here, no matter how small.
在我和我的祖先联系的时候我需要你们保持沉默
I ask for silence now while I reach out to my ancestors.
噢，噢。
Ahh. Ahh.
还好吗？还能呼吸吗？
Are you ok? Can you breathe?
萨姆
Sam.
我无能为力
There's nothing I can do for you.
你们他妈的得离开这儿
You need to get the fuck out of here.
8月4号
额，4号凌晨一点
Uh, 1:00 A.M. on the 4th.
嗯，这么多个晚上的事情后已经没睡过好觉了
Um, already low on sleep after the events of the other night.
萨姆认为我们离具体的那东西越来越近
Sam seems to think we're close to getting something concrete,
某... 某种迹象
some... some kind of evidence.
我承认那个声音，死蝙蝠...
I admit the sound, the dead bats...
的确很奇怪
strange, certainly.
超自然吗？
Paranormal?
我不是很确定
I'm not so sure.
等一下
Hang on.
又怎么了？
So what's up?
过来，雷发现了什么东西
Ray's got something. Come on.
所以我们发现什么了
So what do we got?
就在刚刚，巨大的某种东西触发了
Just a second ago, something very large set off
盲区的一个传感器
one of the sensors in the blind spot.
具体的说是在三区
Zone three, specifically.
所以我们说的是比鹿还大的东西
So we're talking about something bigger than a deer.
快赶上该死的直升机那么大了
Try the size of a god damn helicopter.
好的
All right.
卡梅隆，检查这区域远侧
Cameron, check the far side of the field.
剩下的人，跟着我
The rest of you guys, come with me.
到这儿来
Over here!
这不是自然死亡
This is not a natural death.
动物攻击什么的吗？
What about an animal attack?
哦，不。这儿没有咬痕和爪痕。
Oh, no. There are no bite marks, no claw marks.
这些切口都是完美的
These incisions, they're perfect.
抱歉，小家伙
Sorry, girl.
没有血了
No blood.
这几乎是外科手术
It's almost surgical.
该死的
Shit.
好的，我想把这个小家伙带回去看看
All right, I want to bag the whole thing.
马特，拿袋子过来
Matt, get the bag.
那是什么？
What is it?
萨姆，给点劲，想干嘛的话快点
Come on, Sam, if you're going to do it, do it quick.
8月12号
嘿，丽萨
Hi, Lisa.
嘿，萨姆。嘿，布莱顿
Hey, Sam. Hey, Britain.
嘿
Hey.
血？
Blood?
哦，是的。我昨晚流鼻血了
Oh, yeah. I had a nosebleed last night.
你很容易出鼻血吗？
You prone to nose bleeds?
额，不是的。
Uh, no.
自从来这儿有过几次了
And I've had a couple since I've been here.
我想是这儿海拔的原因或者...
I'm thinking it's just the elevation or...
也许吧
Maybe.
布莱顿，过来
Come on, Britain.
因为她有过几次流鼻血你才知道去查看录像吗？
And you knew to check the tape because she had a few bloody noses?
只是一种感觉
Just a hunch.
我想我们不能告诉他
I don't think we can tell him.
告诉他什么？你怎么解释这个？
Tell him what? How would you even explain this?
不必了。你还想看到更疯狂的东西吗？
You don't. You want to see something even crazier?
这是9号的录像
This is a tape from the 9th.
8月8号
August 8th.
哦，我的天
Oh, my God.
8月7号。每个晚上11点11分
August 7th. 11:11 every night.
雷，现在是什么时间？
Ray, what time is it?
现在是11点过9分
It's 11:09.
马特，什么时候了?
What time is it, Matt?
快10分了。雷，看着摄像头。
It's almost 10 after. Ray, check the camera.
大家伙，发生什么事情了？
You guys, what's going on?
你们在干嘛？萨姆，发生什么事情了？
What are you guys doing? Sam, what's going on?
马特，我要你给我精确数到11点11分
Matt, I need you to give me an exact count up to 11:11.
- 明白吗？ - 好的。摄像头就绪。
- You understand? - All right, camera's good.
- 为什么？ - 摄像头就绪
- Why? - Camera's good.
- 我们现在还多久？ - 现在还有一分钟
- Where are we at right now? - You're at a minute right now.
- 你们这是在干嘛？ - 你能出来一会儿吗？
- What are you guys doing? - Can you come outside for just a second?
可以，可以，好的。等一会儿。你们在干嘛？
Sure. Sure. Yeah. Wait a minute. What are you guys doing?
等等。这是我的房子。你们这是在干嘛？
Wait a second! This is my house.What are you guys doing?
好的，看看吧。在过去的几个夜晚精确到11点11分的时候
All right, look, the last couple of nights at exactly 11:11,
有能量穿过房子
energy has moved through the house.
萨姆，就还有45秒
Sam, you're at 45 seconds.
- 房子里面的能量？ - 是的
- An energy in this house?  - Yeah.
你说“能量”是什么意思？你到底在说什么？
What do you mean "an energy"? What are you talking about?
- 不，我们不需要... - 我们不需要拿枪
- No, we don't need... - You don't need the gun!
还多久？30秒？
Where we at? 30 seconds?
好的，不论你们看到什么
All right, no matter what you see,
不论大家伙看到什么，摄像头都会第一时间记录下来
no matter what you guys see, the camera goes first.
我正要放下呢
I'm putting it down.
好的
Okay.
好的，我们还有10... 9... 8...
Ok, we're at 10... 9... 8...
7... 6... 5...
现在是11点11分
11:11.
没什么嘛！
Nothing.
科迪！科迪！
Cody! Cody!
嘿，科迪！科迪！
Hey, Cody! Cody!
科迪，来和我说说话啊，是爸爸
Cody, buddy, it's daddy.
萨姆，后退点。
Sam, get back.
科迪！
Cody!
科迪。
Cody.
科迪！
Cody!
科迪？
Cody?
马特，丽萨
Matt, Lisa.
进来。
Get in here.
那到底是什么？
What the hell is this?
马特，你去拿好装备
Matt, you go, get her kit.
我们需要记录所有的这些
We need to cast all these prints.
看看这些痕迹。它们到底从哪儿来？
Look at all these tracks. Where did they come from?
这些一定是犬的脚印
These are definitely canine prints.
但它太大了
But they're enormous.
- 有任何发现吗？- 还没有
- Anything?  - Nothing yet.
霍伊特怎么了？
How's Hoyt?
不论好坏，现在他在借酒消愁呢
For better or worse, he's got a lot of alcohol in him now.
那似乎他像是冷静下来了咯
But it seems like he's calmed down.
大家伙注意，我有发现
You guys, I got something.
这上面说“仅供紧急情况”
It says "for emergencies only."
萨姆，那到底是什么？
What the hell is that, Sam?
打个电话现在
Make a call right now.
萨姆
Sam!
无人接听
No one's picking up.
现在还有他们其他的号码吗？
Do you have another number for them?
没有
No.
- 萨姆，有人... - 丽萨，你想我干嘛
- Sam, someone's... - What do you want me to do, Lisa?
我是说...
I'm just saying...
是的
yeah.
我的确是打了电话
I did call, yes.
好，我们...
Well, what we have...
你是说他们到过这儿？
you're saying they were here?
- 从67年到71年。 -做什么？
- From '67 to '71. - Doing what?
注意，你们都搞错了，好吗？
Look, you guys are looking at this the wrong way, ok?
他们回答了我所有的问题
They answered all my questions.
他们主动提供文档记录
They offered to provide documentation.
他们不是想试着去隐瞒什么
They're not trying to hide anything.
他们真那么做了？他们回答了你全部问题... 什么问题？
They did? They answered your question... your questions?
你到底在说神马？
What the hell are you talking about?
霍伊特，他们回答了我所有的问题
They answered all my questions, Hoyt.
我的天，他们真的那样做了吗？
My goodness gracious, they did?
他们没有找到任何东西，好吗？
They didn't find anything, ok?
我现在想和你谈谈
I want to talk to you for a second.
他们到过这！到过这！
They were here. They were here.
等等。等等。且听我一言。
Wait. Wait. Just listen to me one second!
- 听我说！ - 马特
- Listen to me! - Matt!
他们到过这儿？
They were here?
你是要说他们到过这儿吧
You're telling me they were here.
在我的孩子被带走前，他们就到过这儿了
They were here before my boy was taken.
一切为了科学。
Better science.
你就会嚷嚷。你就会嚷嚷
You're just talking. You're just talking.
你能说到什么。别在这儿给我扯淡了
You're not saying anything. You just say, "blah, blah, blah."
那就是你能做的。你只会嚷嚷
That's the way you live your life. You just talk.
我是在讨论这儿的真人真事
I'm talking about something real here.
我在谈论我的孩子的事
I'm talking about my boy.
听着，在打了那个电话之后我才有头绪
Look, we had no idea until I just had that phone call.
但是他们继续呆在这对你的孩子也无能为力
But them being here has nothing to do with your boy.
理解吗？霍伊特？
You understand, Hoyt?
为什么？为什么对我的孩子无能为力？告诉我？
Why? Why does it have nothing to do with my boy? Tell me.
你... 你能告诉我吗？
Do... do you have an answer?
抱歉
Excuse me.
丽萨，你可是个科学家
Lisa, you are a scientist.
你们来调查什么？想试着发现什么？
What are you investigating? What are you trying to find?
你们是来帮我找回孩子的吗？
Are you trying to find my boy?
你们是来帮我找回儿子的吗？
Are you trying to find my son?
看着我的眼睛告诉我你们是来帮我找回儿子的
Just look me in the eye and tell me that you're trying to find my son.
你们是来帮我找回儿子的吗？
Are you trying to find my son?
- 我是来帮你的。 - 那你怎么帮我呢？
- I'm trying to help you. - How you trying to help me?
你来这儿只是为了一己私欲的吧。
You're trying to help yourself.
我已经看透你了
I'm on to you.
你最好得当心点了
You'd better watch out.
最好得当心你自个了啊
You'd better watch yourself.
放下吧。
Put it down.
这就是我要说的
This is what I was telling you about.
伙计们，我发现在窝棚下面埋了两个箱子
Guys, I found two more containers buried in the shed.
我要说的是，发现的第一个箱子里有一根毛
Now, one was empty like the first one I found.
但是第二个里面就藏有这个
But the second had this in it.
- 这是什么？ - 这是卷录像带
- What is this? - It's a U-matic tape.
在60年代末和70年代初很流行
Mostly used in the late '60s and early '70s.
还有，萨姆，这刚好和MDE说的
And, Sam, that would correspond to the timeframe
他们首次来这儿的时间段吻合
that MDE said they were originally on the property.
我不是很清楚我们是否能通过网上的信息来弄明白里面的内容
I'm not sure offhand if we have anything on site I can check this with.
我看看能在里面找到些什么，好吗？
I'll see what I can put together, all right?
8月12号，深夜
Late night. August 12th.
好像MDE在60年代派过人到这儿调查过些事情
Apparently MDE was out here in the '60s looking into this thing.
我们在窝棚下找到的箱子上面写了“仅供紧急情况”
The box we found in the shed said "for emergencies only."
里面什么都没有
And it was empty.
我现在，嗯，更关心的是
I would, uh, probably be more concerned about that
好像我都还没看清楚霍伊特的儿子长什么样子
if I hadn't seen what looked like Hoyt's son
他就穿过了房子
tear through the house,
去了窝棚里面，消失的无影无踪
go into a shed, and completely disappear.
他就那样消失了。我... 我无法解释
He was gone. I... I can't explain it.
我认为萨姆是这么的痴迷去找到
I feel like Sam is so obsessed with finding evidence
这儿所发生的事情的迹象
about what's happening here
以致他都没有去质疑过MDE的动机
that he won't even question MDE's motives.
8月14号
啊！
Aah!
所以，丽萨，你从来没看过那样的东西吗？
So, Lisa, you've never seen anything like this?
没
No.
就是这个
That's it, then.
我们去活捉他
Let's go hunting.
这儿应该有线索，对吧？
There should be tracks, right?
我觉着我们应该找找和窝棚里一样的线索
I think we should be looking for the tracks we found in the shed.
肯定还是那头怪兽
It has to be the same animal.
以我们所见的狼的标准来对比的话
And just judging by the size of the wolf we saw,
这家伙快有500英镑重了，有狼五倍那么大
I'd say it was easily 500 pounds, which is five times larger...
大家伙！
Guys!
那东西超大
That thing is huge.
给点劲，我们过去瞧瞧
Come on, let's go get it.
给点劲，这就是我们来这儿的目的。走起
Come on, that's what we're here for. Go!
现在我们最好步行过去，他就在那儿
We got to go the rest of the way on foot, he's right out there.
好的，走吧
All right, let's go.
放轻松，现在
Easy now.
看看那个，我现在真想回去
Look at that. I want to go back now.
好
Ok.
放轻松。等等。慢一点。我要去那儿
Easy. Wait. Slow down. I'll be right there.
小心点！小心点！
Careful! Careful!
霍伊特，它去哪了？
Hoyt, where'd it go?
我也没看见。小心为好
I don't see it. Be careful.
伙计们，到这儿来
Guys, over here!
等等，萨姆，你看到这个洞口了吗？
Wait, Sam, did you see the light?
- 什么？ - 那有个洞口
- What is it?  - There was a light.
我打赌这是个岩洞
I bet it's a cave system.
我车上有些绳子。我去拿绳子
I got some ropes in my truck. Let me go get 'em.
- 好的。 - 你们小心点
- All right.  - You guys be careful.
那头怪兽还呆在这外面呢
That thing's still out here somewhere.
萨姆，这儿你喜欢吧
Sam, you're gonna want to see this.
你说说那个有多少年份了？
How old do you think that is?
天啊，萨姆，这儿到底发生了什么
Jesus, Sam, what's going on really?
我们看到的到底是什么？
What the hell we even looking at?
雷，看这个！
Ray, look at this!
好像是找到画这些壁画的人了
Looks like we found our artist.
嘘。 嘘
Shh. Shh.
那东西到底是怎么下这儿来的？
How the hell would that thing even get down here?
哦，天啊！快跑！快点！
Oh, God! Go!  Come on!
马特！
Matt!
快点！快点！我说快点啊！我们快跑！
Come on! Come on!  I said hurry! Let's go!
马特，绳子！
Matt, the rope!
布莱顿先！快点，关掉摄像机
Britain first! Come on, turn off the camera.
8月13号。我们...
August 13th. We just...
那头狼，我不知道...
the wolf, I don't know...
早上我们会去了解了解那个壁画的
come and take a closer look at the artwork in the morning.
可能是维摩那，对吗？
Could be a vimana, right?
什么东西？
A what?
维摩那
A vimana.
注：维摩那，古代印度神话传说中遨游天空的飞行器。
啊？
Huh?
在印度，出土的古书籍
In India, they've uncovered all these ancient texts
和文献描述了一种被称作维摩那的外星飞船
and documents that describe a flying spacecraft called a vimana.
我是说，他看起来....他看起来和这个蛮相似的
And I mean, it looks... it looks just like this.
尽管这些东西在有6000年前就有记载
Even though that stuff is, like, 6,000 years old
和很多人认为这是神话
and a lot of people think it's myth,
但是你知道的我们这领域的专家认为
experts in our field think that, you know,
就从其画的原理图和飞行路线图来看
based on the schematics and the flight plans and the design
它和我们今天的科技相吻合
that it's as modern as anything you'd see today.
你是在猜想我们的先祖在岩洞深处
Are you suggesting that our native painted a spacecraft
留下了这些壁画吗？
on the inside of this cave?
是的
Yeah.
正好，我明白我们所看到的了
Just, I know everything we've seen.
那的确很难以置信
That just seems pretty astounding.
- 额，那就像是个完美的巧合。 - 还有这狼呢？
- Well, it's, like, a perfect match.  - And the wolf?
体型比那失踪的孩子和一般的狼都大
This is bigger than a wolf or missing kid.
你怎么知道他会到这儿来
How do you even know he's back here?
他不是正在那忙活他的车子吗
He's working on the ATV.
刚回到那儿我不是有意那样说的
Just wanted to say I completely lost my perspective back there.
还有，嗯
And, uh...
真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
你知道，像那样事情时有发生
Stuff like that happens sometimes, you know.
你知道的，嗯
You know, uh...
科迪，在他生日的那天，用他在那摘的
Cody, on his birthday, he woke his mother up
一束野花把他妈妈给弄醒了
with a handful of wildflowers he picked in that field right out there.
他妈妈看着他，对他说到
And she looked at him, and she said,
“乖孩子，做什么呢...今天可是你的生日。为...为什么送我花呢”
"son, what... it's your birthday. Why... why you giving me flowers?"
他就回答道：“是这样，妈妈，因为有你才有我啊”
And he said, "well, because you're the reason I got born, ma."
那孩子本性就这样
That's the kind of kid he was.
他就这样
He is.
科迪就那样
That's Cody.
听着，嗯
Listen, um,
很抱歉那晚在桌面上让你难堪了
I'm sorry I gave you a hard time the other night at the table.
那... 我不...
It's just... I don't...
我没理解你们所用的方式。还有，嗯....
I don't understand your techniques. And, uh...
我就想让你们知道我很高兴你们能来这儿
I just want you to know I appreciate you're here.
还有，嗯
And, um,
我是说，这是唯一给我带来希望的事了
I mean, it's the only thing that gives me any hope.
没什么
Nothing.
没道理啊
That doesn't make sense at all.
嘘！
Shh!
啊！
Aah!
8月16号
怎么？？
What's the problem?
牧场摄像头失去信号了
The pasture cam's down.
马特，拿着对讲机过那儿去
Matt, take this walkie and go out there.
伙计，不会耽误多少时间的
Won't even take you two minutes, man.
- 好的，萨姆，你能... - 动手啊，马特！
- All right, Sam, can you... - Just do it, Matt!
带我看看室外摄像头的情况
Take me through all the exterior cams.
好的
All right.
听得到吗？
Do you copy?
给我离远30英尺。谢谢了，伙计
Give me 30 feet back for focus. Thanks, buddy.
马特？
Matt?
马特！
Matt!
啊！哦，天啊！
Aah! Oh, my God!
过去！
Go!
马特突然就被那样
Matt's up and about.
他伤的挺严重的，但他应该还好
He's pretty beat up, but he should be fine.
霍伊特的狗所发生的事情，我真不能解释
I have no explanation for what happened to Hoyt's dog.
卡梅隆，可以听到吗？
Cameron, did you hear me?
是的，抱...歉。
Yeah, I'm... sorry.
真的，萨姆，给我退后
Seriously, Sam, just back off.
就是这个意思！
I mean it!
你为什么要这样？
Why are you doing this?
你到底怎么了？
What the hell is wrong with you?
我被刮起来重重的摔倒在地
I was just picked up and thrown.
还有我们对那不可置信的事情，都没有站得住脚的解释
And we don't have a single explanation as to how that's even possible!
听着，我告诉你我决定去干嘛
Look, let me tell you what's going down.
我要去急诊室看看，然后订一张离开这儿的机票
I'm going to the E.R. then I'm booking a flight out of here.
如果你们头脑都清醒的话
And if you guys had, like, an ounce of common sense,
都该跟着我走
you'd all come with me!
糟糕，你们可能要换一个司机了，你们另寻他人吧
You need another driver so bad, you hire someone else.
说真的，大家伙注意安全
Be careful, guys. Seriously.
萨姆，你就是个混蛋。知道不？
You're an asshole, Sam! You know that?
混蛋
Asshole!
我们不是还有霍伊特的车子呢
We still have Hoyt's truck.
我们还可搭乘霍伊特的车
We can go in Hoyt's truck.
雷，发生什么了？
So what's going on, Ray?
你们还记得马特在窝棚找到了有卷录像带的
Are you guys aware that Matt found additional MDE materials in the shed,
MDE材料吗？
including a videotape?
是的，他提过。但是我想那可能太旧了不能播放了吧
Yeah, he mentioned it. But I thought it was too old to play up here.
不。事实是我找到了一台老式磁带机
No. It turns out I was able to find an old deck
并把他改成一个硬件驱动器了
and transfer it to a hard drive.
好。录像带里有什么内容？
Ok. So what was on the tape?
我想大家来一同欣赏会好一点
I think it's better if I just play it for you guys.
那儿，就在那儿
There. Right there.
丽贝卡，能听到吗？
Rebecca, can you hear me?
我们是在车上和丽贝卡回来的路上
We're on our way back in with Rebecca.
离开有个八分钟了
About eight minutes out.
妈妈？妈妈？
Mommy? Mommy?
我妈妈呢？
Where's mommy?
丽贝卡，这就是我们要弄明白的
That's what we're trying to figure out, Rebecca.
你记得你上次和她在一起吗？
You remember the last time you were with her?
她走了多远？
How far out was she?
在牧场外边
Well beyond the pasture.
狗呢？
And the dog?
不知道
No.
她在干些什么？
What's she doing?
米歇尔！
Michelle!
啊。
Ahh.
啊！
Aah!
雷给我们播放了马特在窝棚找到的录像带
Ray played us the tape that Matt had found in the shed.
如果那卷录像带真的可信的话
There's something unexplainable out here.
这儿真发生了无法解释的事情
If that tape is to be believed,
那么我就见证了什么鬼东西
then I just witnessed the killing of an entire team of people
杀死一整个小队的残忍镜头
by something completely unknown.
为什么录像带会放到这儿？
Why would they send us out here?
萨姆对这儿发生的事情可以说是痴迷
Sam is so obsessed with what's happening,
我们犹豫要不要让他看这卷录像带
we're hesitant to even show him the tape.
还有霍伊特...
And Hoyt...
我认为我们该走了
I think we should go.
不得不离开
We have to go.
但此时此刻，我想他不会做出合理的决定的
But I do not think that he is in a place to make decisions right now.
那我们到底该干什么
What the hell are we supposed to do then?
我是说我们今晚就走。我们把霍伊特的车开走
I say we leave tonight. We have Hoyt's truck.
站在我身后
Get behind me.
上车去
Get in the truck.
给我他妈的进车里面去！快点！进车里去！
Get in the fuckin' truck! Go! Get in the truck!
嘿！
Hey!
那东西呢？
Where is it?
丽萨！
Lisa!
该死！
Shit!
这东西他娘的的在干嘛？
What the fuck is it doing?
哦，操蛋！
Ah, shit!
哪...它去哪儿了？
Where did... where did it go?
他跑开了
He just ran off.
丽萨，你还好吗？还好吗？
Are you OK, Lisa? Are you OK?
啊
Aah.
丽萨。别！别！
Lisa, no! No!
你在干嘛？住手！
What are you doing? Stop it!
丽萨，住手！
Lisa, stop!
我什么都记不到了。
I don't remember anything.
真的
Nothing.
我们应该要和马特一起走的
We should've left with Matt.
伙计们，我们正在拍摄绝无仅有的录像呢
We're getting unprecedented footage, guys.
这就是我们想要的啊。我们不就是为了这个才来的吗
This is what we wanted. This is why we came here.
这是我们想要的？有人都受伤了。
This is what we wanted? People are getting hurt.
萨姆，你在胡说些什么？
What are you talking about, Sam?
听着，这是只有我们才掌握的信息
Look, I think the thing is a single intelligence.
哦，为了...  你知道些什么？
Oh, for... you know something?
你疯了
You're out of your mind.
听着，我们如此接近。就差一点
Look, we are so close. We are right there.
接近什么？
Close to what?
要是这东西可以变成宝珠会怎么样？或者狼呢？或者甚至科迪呢？
What if this thing can turn into an orb or a wolf or even Cody?
或者变成我吗？
Or me?
萨姆，说真的，谈话已经他妈的结束了。
Sam, seriously, it's fuckin' done.
萨姆，我不想在这儿呆下去了
I don't want to be here anymore, Sam.
我不能在这儿呆下去了。
I can't be here anymore.
收拾好你的行李。5分钟内在前门碰面
Go pack your bag. I'll meet you at the front door in five minutes.
好的，我们离开吧
Ok, we are leaving.
你不会去哪儿的吧。卡梅隆，求你了。
You're not going anywhere. Cameron, please!
把你的猪蹄子挪开。萨姆，结束了！
Get your hands off me. It's done, Sam!
- 好吧，我可不走。 - 都结束了！别说了！
- Well, I'm not leaving! - It's over! Stop!
8月17号
科迪
Cody.
科迪！
Cody!
布莱顿，我拿了你的包
I got your bag, Britain.
准备好了
I'm ready.
都好了吗
We ready?
萨姆呢？
What about Sam?
他不听劝告。我们叫人再过来
He won't listen. We'll send somebody back.
谁给萨姆灌了药喝？
Who gives a shit about Sam?
雷？
Ray?
卡梅隆，他妈的是什么？
What the fuck is this, Cameron?
哦，天啊。哦，天啊
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
快点！快点！丽萨，我们走吧
Come on. Come on. Let's go, Lisa!
走！
Go!
早上他们会第一时间派辆货车过来
They're sending a van first thing in the morning.
早上？
In the morning?
丽萨，那是到这儿最快的速度了
That's the soonest they can get here, Lisa.
萨姆，那... 太好了
That... that's great, Sam,
想我们出去正准备离开这儿的时候
considering we were just out in Hoyt's driveway
看到他的车已经面目不堪
and his truck was completely disassembled
我们还没遇到过这样见鬼的事呢
and we didn't hear a God damn thing.
- 你们随时离开都行 - 怎样离开？
- Leave anytime you want. - How?
你没发现那很怪吗？
Do you find it odd that the moment we arrived on this ranch
我们一来到这儿这些该死的怪事就接连不断
is when all this shit started happening?
他是对的。我们可能是MDE实验的一部分呢
He's right. We could be part of a MDE experiment...
你在说些什么？你在胡扯吧
what are you talking about? You should know better.
那怎么解释这儿所发生的一切呢？
How do you explain what's been happening here?
萨姆，那你怎么就知道MDE不了解这儿确切的情况呢？
How do you know MDE doesn't know exactly what's here, Sam?
我不应该让你们来这儿的
I never should've asked you to come here.
没事了。我们就要回家了
Ok.We're going to get home.
看着我。我们就要回家了
Look at me.We're going to get home.
卡梅隆，雷好像有点不对劲
Cameron, there's something wrong with Ray.
雷？
Ray?
喔。雷，把枪放下
Whoa. Put the gun down, Ray.
好吗？就... 好的
All right? Just... Ok.
我不想...
I don't want...
不
No!
哦，天啊
Oh, my God!
啊
Aah.
走
Go!
就现在快点！
Come on now!
哦，天啊
Oh, God!
哦，操蛋
Oh, shit.
听我说。你走。你去车子那儿
Listen to me. You go. You get the ATV.
走啊！走啊！
Go! Go!
开门啊！
Open the door!
快开啊！
Open it!
退后点！
Get back!
她不见了。她不见了
She's gone. She's gone.
在饲料仓里面！快点！
In the barn.Hurry!
萨姆
Sam!
喔
Whoa.
快点！快点
Come on. Come on.
卡梅隆
Cameron!
萨姆，等一下
Hang on, Sam!
萨姆
Sam!
啊
Aah!
未来还在继续
The future's holding on
哦，早就该让我撒手
Oh, suspend me in my past
我就这样醒来
And this is how I woke up
独自一人
Alone
细绳把你荡在
You're dangling by a string
万事之上
Above everything you could be
你就这样醒来
And this is how you woke up
独自一人
Alone
借用你的脖子
Sharpen their teeth
磨出一口尖牙
On your neck
还记得你的缺陷
Remember your flaws
就像一个坏坏的梦
Like a bad dream
你执意要醒来
You want to wake up
快醒来吧
Please wake up
哦，快醒来吧
Oh, please wake up
Oh, please wake up!
哦，快醒来吧
哦，还有时间
Oh, there's still time
我们凝望一刻也好
Just for a moment as we stare
在空气中注入我们的思念
Projecting our thoughts into the air
要是以前就这样该多好
As if we had practiced it before
我们手拉手让思想纵容
Our minds danced hand in hand /i>
我们的生活早已注定
And choreographed by both our lives
用眼睛讲述相同的故事
Told like stories to our eyes
世界迟早都会安静
All of the world frozen in time
我们就这样醒来
And this is how we woke up
还记得自己是谁
And we remember who we are
我们穿过黑暗
We were passing in the dark
仿佛就沐浴在阳光下面
As if we're something in the light
你知道我们都很极端
We're left you know
都很极端
Left you know!
那一刻你不再失败
When you won't even fail